<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wheels</string>

    <!-- Main Screen -->
    <string name="wheels_logo">Wheels Logo</string>
    <string name="search_button">Find Wheels</string>
    <string name="xxr_banner">XXR Banner</string>
    <string name="bolt_pattern_button">Find Bolt Pattern</string>

    <!-- App Menu -->
    <string name="menu_find_wheels">Find Wheels</string>
    <string name="menu_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="menu_find_bolt_pattern">Find Bolt Pattern</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Help Activity -->
    <string name="help_logo">Help Logo</string>
    <string name="help_content_main"><b>How to use the search?</b>\nSelect the vehicle that you want
        to find wheels and tires for\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="help_content_other"><b>Tire Type</b>\nThe letter \"P\" at the beginning of the \"Tire Size\"
        tells us the tire is a P-Metric tire, referring to tires made to certain standards within the
        United States, intended for Passenger vehicles.\n\nIf a tire size has no letters at the
        beginning, this indicates a Euro metric tire. P-Metric and Euro-Metric tires may have
        different load capacities.\n\nThe letters \"LT,\" either at the beginning or at the end of the
        tire size indicate the tire was designed for light trucks. Vehicle manufacturers equip some
        light trucks with \"LT\" type tires. These tires generally require higher inflation pressures
        than passenger tires.\n\nConsult your owner\'s manual or tire placard for the recommended
        tire size and inflation pressure for your vehicle.\n\n<b>Tire Width</b>\nIs the width of the
        tire measured in millimeters from sidewall to sidewall. The first three-digit number in the
        tire size refers to the tire width. For instance, in a size P215/65 R15 tire, the width is
        215 millimeters.\n\n<b>Aspect Ratio</b>\nIs the ratio of the height of the tire\'s cross-section
        to its width. The two-digit number after the slash mark in a tire size is the aspect ratio. For
        example, in a size P215/65 R15 tire, the 65 means that the height is equal to 65% of the
        tire\'s width. The bigger the aspect ratio, the bigger the tire\'s sidewall will be.\n\n<b>Construction</b>\n
        The letter \"R\" in a tire size stands for Radial, which means the layers run radially
        across the tire.\n\n<b>Wheel Diameter</b>\nIs the size of the wheel measured from one end to
        the other. It tells us the size of the wheel that the tire is intended to fit. A size P215/65 R15 tire is made
        for a wheel with a 15\" diameter.\n\n<b>Load Index</b>\nIndicates the maximum load that the
        tire can support when properly inflated. You\'ll also find the maximum load on the tire sidewall,
        in both pounds and kilograms.\n\n<b>Speed Rating</b>\nTells you the maximum speed capability
        of a tire. Often speed ratings are matched to the top speed capability of the vehicle. For
        example, a tire with an H-speed rating has a maximum speed capability of 130 mph or 210 km/h.
        Goodyear does NOT recommend exceeding legally posted speed limits.\n\n<b>DOT Symbol</b>\nThe letters
        \"DOT\" on the sidewall indicate that the tire complies with all applicable Federal Motor
        Vehicle Safety Standards in the United States.\n\nTo view more information,
        visit:\n<b><a href="https://www.goodyearautoservice.com/en-US/tire-basics/tire-size">goodyearautoservice.com</a></b>\n\n
    </string>

    <!-- Search -->
    <string name="enter_vehicle_hint">2019 Subaru WRX STi</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="settings_name">Name</string>
    <string name="settings_save_button">Save Preferences</string>

</resources>
